The entire neighborhood is in shock as to where she is bringing such a big
parcel from and I am
not able to lift it and while lifting it it
fell.  After getting insulted, let's
unbox this big parcel which
starts from ₹10 and has all the Masoom
Fines which you must need now.  The first one
is this racket which is the mosquito killer
racket.  I bought it for just ₹115 and it is
very useful.  There is no mercy for mosquitoes.
Now the next product is very
cute which is something like this
and this is a mini dustbin which I got for ₹75
and if you keep stationery etc. then
you can buy this in which
you can keep small papers.  Apart from that, you should definitely
buy this chopper which is for ₹17.
Next is this flower pot which is very
cute.  A set of five comes for
₹165 and it also includes these type of plates
and they look very cute.
And its size was also quite good, friend.  I did
not have such high expectations but it is much better than Duo Dub.
Apart from that
I have bought mosquito killer lamps.  Hopefully
this will work.  Apart from that,
I bought this drain cleaner for ₹30 and
I bought all these from Doop.  You can also take it.
So now